<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:fillViewport="true"
    android:paddingBottom="64dp"
    >

    <androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        tools:context=".ui.HomeSelectFragment">

        <!-- TODO: Update blank fragment layout -->
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:text="My favorite childhood toys reflect the places I lived in when I was young. My favorite toy as a child of seven years old was the dried fallen branches in the woods. There was a small one behind our house and it provided endless fun for me and my brothers and sisters. Collected sticks and branches became our castle, our fort, and our play home. Wood pieces gave us play swords, fishing rods, umbrellas, and jungle gyms. They were my best childhood toy because they contained so many other toys. What I most loved to play with at eight years old was dirt marbles. We lived in a neighborhood where there was an eternal pit of mud on the strip of grass in front of our apartment. My brothers and I would mix the smooth mud with sand from the side of the road, roll it into balls and leave them to dry in the hot afternoon sun. We would hit them against each other to gain points and arm our slingshots with them. The toy of my last year of elementary school that I obsessed about was stickers. At that time we lived in a narrow alley with shophouses all long it and we children would buy from there stickers and products that included free stickers of robots, cartoon characters, and spaceships that we would collect, trade, or compete for in sticker flipping games. My cherished toy as a new teenager was my bicycle. We lived in a soi with lots of pavement and no cars. I was head of the bike gang and we would set up ramps for jumps and design obstacle courses for racing. Now I have started university and am no longer a child but I think happily of these toys of childhood which show a history of where I have been and what Bangkok used to be, thankful for the young adult that I am because of them.My favorite childhood toys reflect the places I lived in when I was young. My favorite toy as a child of seven years old was the dried fallen branches in the woods. There was a small one behind our house and it provided endless fun for me and my brothers and sisters. Collected sticks and branches became our castle, our fort, and our play home. Wood pieces gave us play swords, fishing rods, umbrellas, and jungle gyms. They were my best childhood toy because they contained so many other toys. What I most loved to play with at eight years old was dirt marbles. We lived in a neighborhood where there was an eternal pit of mud on the strip of grass in front of our apartment. My brothers and I would mix the smooth mud with sand from the side of the road, roll it into balls and leave them to dry in the hot afternoon sun. We would hit them against each other to gain points and arm our slingshots with them. The toy of my last year of elementary school that I obsessed about was stickers. At that time we lived in a narrow alley with shophouses all long it and we children would buy from there stickers and products that included free stickers of robots, cartoon characters, and spaceships that we would collect, trade, or compete for in sticker flipping games. My cherished toy as a new teenager was my bicycle. We lived in a soi with lots of pavement and no cars. I was head of the bike gang and we would set up ramps for jumps and design obstacle courses for racing. Now I have started university and am no longer a child but I think happily of these toys of childhood which show a history of where I have been and what Bangkok used to be, thankful for the young adult that I am because of them."
            android:textSize="20sp" />

    </androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>

</ScrollView>